我能使用的工具实在太少了。”
I have so few tools to deal with."
这是一个可怕的疾病，
It's a terrifying disease,
人们肺里插着呼吸机独自死去。
to die alone with a ventilator in your lungs,
而且这是一个 会影响身体所有器官的疾病。
and it's a disease that affects all of our organs.
它是一个呼吸道疾病 ——
It's a respiratory disease --
这么说也许存在一定的误导性，
perhaps misleading.
因为它让你联想到流感。
Makes you think of a flu.
但非常多的病人尿液中有血，
But so many of the patients have blood in their urine
这是源自肾脏疾病。
from kidney disease,
他们还会得肠胃炎，
they have gastroenteritis,
经常伴有心脏衰竭。
they certainly have heart failure very often,
我们知道它还会影响 味觉和嗅觉、嗅神经，
we know that it affects taste and smell, the olfactory nerves,
当然，我们还知道它对肺部的损害。
we know, of course, about the lung.